EPISODE 4
THE DREAM PLACE
FOR START-UPS
ACCEPTING APPLICATIONS
FOR SAND BOX'S 12TH RESIDENCY PROGRAM
A PLACE WHERE YOUR DREAMS COME TRUE
I WANT TO LAUNCH MY START-UP BECAUSE
I WANT TO BE AN INSPIRING CEO
I WANT TO TAKE…
Even when you think your code is complete…
I DON'T WANT TO…
…one missing conditional can create a bug
and crash your program.
BUG: AN ERROR IN THE SOURCE CODE
I WANT TO TURN…
There was one conditional in particular,
"If Sand Box is everyone's dream…"
APPLICATION FOR THE 12TH
SAND BOX RESIDENCY PROGRAM
WON IN-JAE, NAM DO-SAN, SEO DAL-MI
I overlooked this one conditional
and this is
the result of it.
Who do you choose,
me or Seo Dal-mi?
Do-san.
A bug occurred, and I crashed.
1. PLAYGROUND FILLED WITH SAND
TO PREVENT INJURIES
2. TEST ENVIRONMENT FOR DEVELOPERS
3. POSTPONEMENT OF REGULATIONS
FOR THE RELEASE OF NEW PRODUCTS
Dal-mi, wipe the drool
and sleep in your bed.
-Grandma, I have a business idea.
-Yes?
A restaurant you can start with no money.
Restaurants that only have kitchens,
in one place.
A restaurant needs more than a kitchen.
Where will the customers sit?
They won't.
It'll be delivery-only.
No interior design,
and no tables or chairs.
Just a kitchen.
Since you don't need much capital,
it's no big deal even if you fail.
Mother, listen to this.
-What?
-A website that displays all the leaflets.
Instead of looking at leaflets,
you go to the website
and browse all the delivery restaurants
by category.
Dad, how about introducing
a ranking system?
There will be five different classes.
-That sounds great.
-Dal-mi, that's a brilliant idea.
We'll let the customers
review the restaurants.
If the ratings are high…
Dad.
What do we do now?
What?
It's okay.
It's no big deal.
Don't worry too much. It's okay.
Simply put, it's like a coworking space,
but it's for restaurants.
Not interesting? Okay, let's move on.
Grandma.
How about cars that don't need keys?
Instead, we can use
biometrics authentication.
With fingerprint scanners, you won't
have to carry around your car keys.
No, wait.
Facial recognition would be better.
It's a hassle to take off your gloves
when it's cold.
-Dal-mi.
-Yes?
Running a business
is hard. You know that, right?
Of course.
But it's not as hard as before.
Even high schoolers
start businesses these days.
Also, I might have found a way.
What way?
It's a secret.
I'll tell you if I get in.
Just tell me now.
I don't want to.
It'll be embarrassing if I don't get in.
Facial recognition, not fingerprints.
My gosh. Unbelievable.
Good morning.
Hi.
Let's start the meeting.
Where are the others?
Gosh. I am totally against the flexible
working hour idea. I think it's stupid.
Please come to meetings on time.
Tell the ones that are not here yet
to come right now.
Let's get started.
The thing is… Here, sir.
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
What are these?
I'm sorry to say this
when you trusted and followed me.
But I might not be able to pay you
for the time being.
We also won't get an office anytime soon.
I like it. It feels like we're making
a fresh start.
Not many offices
come with Jacuzzis, do they?
-You're right.
-That aroma oil does wonders.
All my wrinkles and spots are gone.
Your eyes are aging,
so you don't see them.
They're not gone.
You…
Who are these people?
If you don't see the spots on your face,
get glasses.
Wait. Should she consider it a blessing
and do nothing?
Don't tell me you're using
my hotel room as your office.
I am. Please bear with me
until I get into Sand Box.
There, I can rent an office for free
and pay my employees.
Sorry to interrupt your meeting.
We need to talk.
Sand Box? Why would you get in there?
Isn't that a place for people
with no money or connections?
Exactly.
I need to succeed
with no money or connections.
Why? You have money and connections.
I'm not divorced yet.
Is that why you're putting up with this?
To give me money and connections?
Didn't you thank me for giving you
a rich dad?
I am thankful.
As long as I have a rich dad,
I can't take any credit.
I'm not even acknowledged by my own mom.
I learned that thanks to you.
Are you serious?
You think it's easy
to start a business from zero?
Are you doing this to make me worry?
"Worry"?
Why is it so infuriating
to hear you say you worry about me?
Do you worry about one
and encourage the other?
Bluffing without a real plan
makes you a fraud.
Sorting things out afterward
makes you the same as your father.
I'm rooting for you.
In-jae, I just--
If you acknowledge me,
don't worry about me. Just encourage me.
YOON SEON-HAK'S SAND BOX
JOINING SAND BOX Q AND A
I grabbed it first.
Too bad. I grabbed it before you did.
Why would a lawyer apply for Sand Box?
Law is just a hobby. I'm a designer.
Why are you applying, then?
Because I have nothing. No connections,
no credentials, and no money.
-What's your name?
-It's Seo Dal-mi.
-Why?
-To steer clear of you.
I have nothing to gain from you.
What's your name?
It's Jung Sa-ha. Why?
I have a lot to gain
from someone competent like you.
You want to leech off me
but can't give up the book for me?
I'll give you 1,000 won.
Give up the book for me.
I'll give you 5,000.
Deal.
Give up so easily?
What a crook.
JOINING SAND BOX Q AND A
How many bookstores have we visited?
Oh, they have them here.
Ask her.
Excuse me.
Could you tell me
where you found that book?
In the Start-up section.
-Thank you.
It's over there.
Okay.
Too bad. This was the last one.
Really?
Gosh, we've been going around
all the bookstores in the neighborhood.
How many?
This is the sixth.
How about this?
Give me 10,000 won,
and the book is yours, darlings.
What?
Guys, what do you think it means
when a girl calls you darling?
-What are you talking about?
-I mean the girl from earlier.
She gave up the book for us
and called us darlings
when we just met.
-Do you think she was hitting on us?
-Was she hitting on us?
Oh, my. I can't believe this.
Was she hitting on us, Do-san?
What?
Give me that.
Here.
Goodness.
JOINING SAND BOX Q AND A
-I dropped my earring.
-Me, too. No, I mean…
-Hello.
-Why are you here?
-I'm getting a book about San--
San Francisco. About Silicon Valley.
That's right.
Our company is going global soon.
Already going global? That's impressive.
No, there's nothing impressive about us.
Isn't he so humble?
Where's your car?
My car?
I slept over at Chul-san's last night.
The alley is pretty narrow,
so I didn't take my car.
And that explains my lousy outfit.
Did you hear what that betrayer said?
I think it's nice and casual.
Until now, you looked so perfect
that it made me uncomfortable.
I'm far from perfect.
What are you doing tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
Nothing much.
-Really?
-Yes.
You have no plans for your birthday?
-My birthday?
-Yes.
His birthday isn't for a while.
I guess it's Mr. Han's.
He wrote those letters.
Oh, it is my birthday tomorrow.
It slipped my mind.
Do you remember writing to me
about your wish?
My wish?
Of course, I do.
I'll make that wish come true tomorrow.
Okay.
Don't make any plans.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Hey! What are you doing?
Thank you.
What is he thinking?
I approve.
-You're jealous, aren't you?
-Of that?
Don't be stupid. Absolutely not.
Jealousy is…
-for losers.
-Don't cry.
Let's go.
Shouldn't you go back to work?
I will after I take you home.
Goodness, I'm not a kid.
Your hand…
My hand? What about it?
I thought my hands are pretty big,
but they look tiny next to yours.
Oh…
-Do-san?
-Yes?
Do-san.
Yong-san, did you know I have huge hands?
How can it make me so happy?
I must be crazy.
Don't go crazy now. Come.
-What's wrong?
-Just come.
Hurry.
Line up, please!
-Give me one.
-You'll get one.
Please wait! Whatever, just take them all!
-What's going on?
-The news about CODA is finally out.
Don't worry. You'll get one.
Gosh, why do you show up so late
when you're the CEO?
-He's the CEO?
-The CEO is here!
You won the CODA competition?
-Hello.
-Can we have a meeting, please?
-We'd like a meeting.
-Calm down.
-We're GT Electronics.
-They all want to invest?
This is it. We're going big now.
-Take my business card!
-Thank you.
-Calm down!
Nice to meet you all.
All right.
Let's get started.
Our company is called Samsan Tech.
Kim Yong-san, Lee Chul-san,
and Nam Do-san.
That's where our name comes from.
Three Sans.
We'd love to hear
about your business model.
Oh, sure.
Just a moment.
Take your time.
CONTENT
When learning image recognition,
there is a trade-off
between network size and accuracy.
-Here, you see--
-I get it.
I see how great your technology is,
but how are you going to make money?
Money?
To raise accuracy,
the quantity has to increase,
making the learning harder.
To solve that, our learning architecture--
So you don't have
a clear revenue model yet?
We'll discuss it and get back to you.
It all sounds brilliant,
but I'm afraid it's not
our main field of interest.
Thanks for the explanation.
I appreciate it.
-There.
-Thank you.
As you can see,
since our network is so slim,
it requires shorter training time
and is easy to implement.
Oh, my. Give them a big hand.
This is amazing.
So it's not reinforcement through
adding feature maps. Is that right?
That's right.
As you can see here,
we connect the feature maps together.
-Can we see the next page?
-Sure. Next page.
Here's the next page.
Take close-ups if you want.
This is worth the wait.
The future of Samsan Tech--
Are you stupid? You want to hand
your technology to them on a plate?
I've never seen you. Where do you work?
Are you sure you're VCs,
not here to steal their technology?
VC: INVESTOR THAT PROVIDES CAPITAL
TO VENTURES
SAMSAN TECH INNOVATIONS
You're developers, aren't you?
What's this photo?
Look, we need to verify their technology
before investing--
Give me back my ID card.
Your business card says you're a VC,
but your ID card says
you lead the deep learning team.
DEEP LEARNING TEAM MANAGER
Which is true?
Let's go, guys.
Okay.
I didn't even like the design of this.
What is this, traffic lights?
-Let's go.
-Gosh.
SAMSAN TECH
ON STANDBY 24/7
Are you naive or stupid?
Were you going to give away
the whole algorithm?
They said they wanted to see
our technology before investing.
You should've found out who they are.
Isn't that common sense?
And what? You want to get into Sand Box?
Dream on.
But we won the CODA competition.
And you saw how many investors
are showing interest.
So what?
Have any of them gotten back to you?
No.
Is your job discouraging people?
Why are you always so critical?
None of the VCs we met today
were harsh like you.
Because they're going to turn you down!
This isn't the car they're going to ride.
That's why they just compliment it.
On the other hand, I want to know
about the tires, the lining. All of it.
Because I might actually ride it.
Because I actually am interested!
I'm sorry.
From now on, ask me
before you make any decision.
Understood?
Yes.
We've officially become his underlings.
On that note, let me ask you something.
What is it?
I ran into
Dal-mi earlier.
-In those clothes?
-I told her they're Chul-san's.
Chul-san's?
Okay.
I didn't know you could be
so shameless and quick-witted.
Dal-mi said that tomorrow
is my birthday.
It's my birthday tomorrow.
Did I write that in the letters?
Do you remember writing
about your wish, too?
Dal-mi said she'd make my wish come true.
My wish?
-I don't remember it.
-I see.
You don't remember it? Are you serious?
What should Do-san do then?
-What do you mean?
-Exactly.
Do-san is only dealing with
that Dal-mi girl
because you asked him to.
And what's this attitude of yours?
In that case, we can't cooperate.
-Only because I asked him to?
-Yes.
Do-san wants nothing to do with girls.
You could call him a modern-day hermit.
Yes, and now he's going
to all this trouble
just to save Samsan Tech.
Is that right?
I didn't realize
you were such an ambitious man.
Well, yes. I am ambitious.
You're ambitious…
I don't know what you owe and to whom…
But I doubt you can pay your debt
without Do-san's help.
And you've got the nerve
to treat us like this?
You're basically making it impossible
for us to cooperate.
I'm making it…
I'm making it impossible?
You're doing a great job.
And I'm thankful.
Please keep up the good work.
Okay.
We've taken the high ground now.
Don't hesitate to ask me anything.
Okay.
Hey, sit comfortably.
You should.
This is your office, after all.
-Grandma!
-Gosh, you startled me.
I'd finally threaded the needle.
I'll do it for you.
Grandma, can I borrow your blanket?
My blanket? Why?
I'm going on a date.
Do-san and I are going
on our first official date tomorrow.
-There you go. I'll put it here.
-Okay.
-Thanks.
-No problem.
Why does she need a blanket, though?
Hey. Why do you need a blanket on a date?
It's Do-san's birthday tomorrow.
I'll make his wish come true.
What does a blanket have
to do with his birthday?
Is it just me?
My imagination is running wild.
Your imagination? Like what?
It's absolutely
unspeakable.
What?
Grandma. This is what we're going to do.
Oh…
Come on.
You had me panicking.
That looks good.
There you go. You look amazing.
This fits me perfectly
unlike the previous one,
which was too short.
"Too short"? You're just
a couple of centimeters taller than me.
Really? I'm 187cm tall. What about you?
I bought this one for you.
And these ones here, too.
All of them?
Put on this watch.
This looks really expensive.
-It's more than the car.
-What?
I'm not giving you this.
Use it carefully and return it. Okay?
Be careful.
Be absolutely careful, okay?
I'm curious, Mr. Han.
Why are you going to all this trouble?
Like I said, I'm trying to pay my debt.
How in debt are you
that it can't be paid with your wealth?
I wish it could be paid with money.
-This is the salad fork.
-The salad fork.
-The dessert fork.
-Yes, that's right.
-Okay.
This is how you drink wine.
First, swirl your glass.
No, not so vigorously.
Swirl just slightly.
Now, sniff it.
Not so loudly. Just enjoy the aroma.
-The aroma?
-Slowly.
No, not like that.
There's no need to inhale so deeply.
Do-san is an avatar.
I wonder if he can look like a CEO
by doing that.
Just have a quick sniff.
That's enough. Put down your glass.
That's it. Good.
We don't drink it?
Go over it again.
-Which is the salad fork?
-Now.
I mean, which is the salad fork?
This.
-Now, find the dessert fork.
-Okay.
Have you two never dated either?
It's not because we haven't wanted to.
What does that mean?
Does that mean you tried?
Yes, we sure have.
There are
considerably fewer girls than guys
in the Engineering Department.
Yes, to get more chances to meet girls,
we even started a club.
What kind of club?
There you go. It's done.
CLUB ROOM
We should close the door.
We're not open yet. But soon.
A knitting club.
Knitting?
That's how desperate we were.
But instead of girls…
Nam Do-san came. To actually knit.
There were, of course, a few girls
who came to join the club now and then.
But there was no point.
Once a girl asked,
"Do-san, have you always been single?"
And he answered,
"Maybe. But I like to mingle."
He drove the girl away
with his lame jokes.
One day, another girl
almost joined our club.
She said, "Do-san, thanks for letting me
borrow your notes,"
giving him a present.
He said, "I'm the one
who should thank you now."
Everything was going well
until the girl said,
"I'm twice as thankful as you are."
"That means neither of us is thankful.
Let's say your gratitude is A,
and mine is B.
B is larger than A, but A equals 2B.
For that to be true,
both A and B should be negative numbers.
In other words, what we're feeling is
the opposite of gratitude."
That's how he drove that girl away.
Once, a sexy and a bit older girl said,
"I heard you're blood type O.
People with blood type O
tend to be easygoing and honest."
Do-san answered seriously,
"Personalities are determined
by your brain cells." She said, "Yes."
"Blood types are determined
by your red blood cells." "Yes."
"Normally, your brain cells never come
into contact with your red blood cells.
So how could your blood type
affect your personality?
Gosh, this is driving me freaking crazy.
Darn it."
I'm blood type O, too.
Like that, he practically
kicked the girl out.
So what you're saying is,
even though it wasn't intentional…
He ended up driving all the girls away.
And because of him,
we haven't had any girlfriends either.
Now that I think of it,
we're that punk's victims.
Did you say this is the salad fork?
-No! The dessert fork!
-The dessert fork!
-Gosh.
-Seriously.
-See you later, Grandma.
-Dal-mi.
Take this.
-What is this?
-A birthday present.
Tell him it's from me to the Nam Do-san
in the old days. He'll understand.
-"The Nam Do-san in the old days"?
-Yes.
Okay.
-See you, ma'am.
-See you, young lady.
-See you.
-Bye.
Be natural.
Don't cross your legs or anything.
What was that noise? What just happened?
Don't try to look cool, okay?
Okay.
You still don't remember your wish?
Well, I'm sure it's some kind of present.
Don't forget to thank her.
-What's that?
-It's a present from my grandma
to the Nam Do-san in the old days.
The Nam Do-san in the old days? That's me.
Where are we going?
To your home? Your office?
-My home?
-Your office?
We should go somewhere inside
to play Go-Stop.
-Go-Stop?
You said your wish was to play Go-Stop.
-I did?
-Why?
That's what I should be asking.
Why Go-Stop?
I have no idea. I wonder why.
I don't remember it.
You might remember it
once we start playing.
Oh, call your friends over, too.
-You wanted to play with many people.
-My friends?
So where are we going?
Your home? Your office?
Well… Let me get that.
Let's go to my office.
Your office? Which one?
Hello? Which one?
-The one by the Han River, remember?
-Yes.
-Let's go there.
-Sure.
We're going to the one by the Han River.
By the Han River?
Here?
Hello? Did he hang up? Hello?
I don't have the phone number
of Samsan Tech.
Hurry up.
-To the right.
We don't have much time.
-Don't get angry.
-Help me.
Can't you do it alone?
You obviously can't. There you go.
-Hurry up and come here.
-I'm coming.
-Take this.
-Give it to me.
-One,
-No.
two, three.
-Put this away first.
-Isn't that a good photo?
-It is.
-Okay.
Wait, that's not how you do it.
-This feels like our office now.
-I agree.
-Does this go here?
-Yes.
-The one above that.
-What?
I don't think this is the right one.
It's just that you're bad.
You're taking a whole day.
I'm almost done. Give me just a second.
I'm done. Should we turn on the monitor?
Please don't touch it. You might break it.
You should get changed, too.
What do you think?
-It's perfect. Good job.
-I picked navy.
They're almost here.
Hurry up and get changed.
Hurry. But don't drop anything.
-I'll be cleaning up over there.
-Okay.
Hurry up.
Gosh.
-Welcome.
-Hello.
-Hi.
It's your first date.
Why the hell did you come here?
The weather is lovely.
You could've enjoyed the sun somewhere.
Mr. Han, we meet again.
Hi.
I'm really interested in their company.
I come here often.
As if it were my own office.
I see.
-That's a perfect spot.
-Where?
Do you all know how to play Go-Stop?
Go-Stop?
Do you remember why you wanted to play?
No. It's been too long. I forgot.
Anyway, try to relax. Be natural.
Put on a little smile.
Oh, my. What is all this?
It's a feast.
Songpyeon?
Why songpyeon on a birthday,
not sirutteok?
-Ta-da.
-Oh, my!
Unbelievable. She made so much.
Do-san.
My dad says praying on the full moon
on Chuseok makes your wish come true.
Do you have any wishes?
My wish…
-Four generations of family members
-My wish…
are gathered together.
The whole family played traditional games
they'd never played before such as
spinning tops and neolttwigi.
Families that stayed indoors
spent the day playing games
such as Go-stop and Yut Nori.
TO DAL-MI
MY WISH IS…
This Chuseok, the whole family gathered
for the first time in a long time…
MY WISH IS TO PLAY GO-STOP
WITH MY WHOLE FAMILY
-But I don't see any galbi.
-This is enough.
I'm just joking!
-Laugh harder.
-It's okay if it's cold.
The microwave is over there… Right?
Yes, that's right.
Here we go.
Let's begin.
Hurry up.
Isn't it such a weird wish, though?
I know. Why would playing Go-Stop
be anyone's wish?
You play Go-Stop on holidays every year.
Right, Mr. Han?
Well, I'm…
To someone,
it might have a special meaning.
What's ordinary to one person
can be extraordinary to another.
He probably has fond memories of it.
Maybe he really enjoyed playing it
with his family on the holidays.
Or maybe it wasn't ordinary at all to him
and made him envious.
-Right?
-Right.
-What?
I can relate.
I've been there.
Oh, really?
Let's get started now.
-Hurry up.
-Come on.
-Let's get started.
-Okay.
-Here you go.
-Well…
-Let me see.
-Here.
Gosh, I'm screwed.
Stop! Do-san has five gwangs.
Do I win five points then?
No, you win 15 points.
Yong-san and Mr. Han have no gwangs.
You're not allowed to help him.
-It's against the rules.
-Be quiet!
-How much is it then?
-3,000 won.
-It's 3,000 won.
You're supposed to learn by losing.
-You shouldn't help him.
-Give me that.
Here we go.
Oh, my goodness.
What's useless to you is valuable to me
now. Yes! It's all mine. Give it to me.
Give it to me!
Stop what you're doing.
I pulled another matching card.
The tables have turned, Chul-san.
I win, Chul-san!
Hurry and pay up.
So who wins?
What was this called? This is a sweep!
You guys have to give me one
of your pi cards.
Give me a pi card.
Don't throw the cards like that. God…
Seriously.
Do you like eating crumbs?
I'm not eating this. It's plastic.
You guys think that's funny?
It's not funny, Mr. Nam.
What are you talking about?
It's hilarious.
Mr. Han, just let it go.
Is your blood type A?
It shows from the way you play Go-Stop.
You're definitely blood type A.
-Right?
-What?
Clearly, considering how timid
and unforgiving he is.
-Unbelievable.
-See?
Do-san, you're putting aside
your beliefs for a girl?
Dal-mi, the thing is…
He doesn't believe
in blood type personalities.
Really? You don't?
I do.
Galileo Galilei must have felt this way
when he denied heliocentrism.
Exactly. Still, the Earth
revolves around the Sun.
No, I really believe it.
-I can't believe you.
-I'm sweating.
-You punk.
-I am blood type A.
You are? I knew it.
Please thank your grandma for me.
Why don't you thank her yourself?
I'm sure she'd love to see you.
I've never met her.
No. I'll visit her properly
some other time.
All right. I had so much fun today.
Me, too.
Bye.
Wait, Dal-mi.
Yes?
What do you like about me?
What?
Why all of a sudden?
Please tell me what you like about me.
First of all,
you're my first love.
That's not me.
And?
Your letters
comforted me for a long time.
That's not me either.
And?
And…
after all these years,
you're still so brilliant and cool.
Again,
that's not me.
And?
You want to hear more?
You have nice, big hands.
My hands?
Why are you suddenly asking this?
You're embarrassing me.
I'm sorry. That was random.
Go inside. I'll get going.
-Okay. Good night.
-Good night.
YOU PASSED THE 1ST SCREENING
AND ARE QUALIFIED FOR THE HACKATHON
Oh, my God!
Dal-mi, is that you?
YOU PASSED THE 1ST SCREENING
Yes, I'm home.
Yes!
YOU PASSED THE 1ST SCREENING
AND ARE QUALIFIED FOR THE HACKATHON
Have some coffee.
-Thank you.
Ms. Choi.
Is Dal-mi home yet?
Yes. She was in such a good mood
that she danced in the entrance.
Really?
Thank you, Good Boy.
Why do you keep thanking me?
I haven't done anything much.
Also, why did you send so much food?
It's the least I can do.
Thanks to you,
Dal-mi's confidence is soaring.
Isn't that a good thing? Why do you sigh?
I'm worried she'll fall
and get hurt.
She won't get hurt.
I'll make sure
she doesn't.
The Sand Box Success Story…
The Start-up Bible…
BAEDAL.COM BUSINESS PLAN
CEO SEO CHEONG-MYEONG
DADDY, PLEASE ORDER A BUFFET
ON MY BIRTHDAY
You did a good job today.
-Here.
-Oh, yes.
The suits are here.
Take them with you. You can have them.
No. I'll buy my own clothes.
Come on.
-Your sense of style--
-I know.
It's awful.
But I'll change.
-Why suddenly draw the line?
-I'm respecting the line.
If I take them, it's not an investment.
It's charity.
Just give me some tips
whether it's on my style or business.
I'll follow them no matter what.
-No matter what?
-Yes.
What if I tell you to recruit a CEO
for your company?
Pardon?
That's my tip.
Give up your CEO position.
You're not cut out to be a CEO.
You'll only make everyone's life harder.
Once you enter Sand Box,
recruit a CEO first.
What your company needs is a proper CEO.
Are you saying
I'll never become a good CEO?
Yes.
Hey, what are you doing here?
Wonders never cease!
I have a desperate wish.
Lord is busy.
He has no time to listen to the prayer
of an unfaithful believer like you.
Lord,
listen to the prayers
of unfaithful believers
in order to make them faithful.
That's what we call business
and marketing.
Cut the crap.
What is this desperate wish
of yours, anyway?
And what's that luggage?
Sister, shouldn't you keep it down
in the church?
What's that luggage?
Are you running away from home?
Father, Mother.
I passed the first screening of Sand Box.
I don't even get excited anymore.
You tell us you passed this and that
all the time,
but nothing ever changes.
If you passed the first screening,
what's the next step?
The next step will be
a competition called a hackathon.
Each team is given three days
to come up with a business model.
You have to win the competition
to enter Sand Box.
At Sand Box,
you're given an office,
and they even pay your employees.
Besides, investors will--
Whatever.
Just tell us when you actually get in.
I've had enough of your empty promises.
Okay.
-See you.
That rude brat.
Did you see how he just slammed the door?
He's rebelling against me, isn't he?
If I were him, I'd smash that door.
Is it so hard to wish him good luck?
Why did you have to put him down
like that?
I said that as his parent.
Can't I say that much?
It hurts even more
because it's from his parent!
Well, Father.
It was
the wind.
What?
It's very windy outside.
I didn't mean to slam the door.
I don't want you to get the wrong idea.
I'll get going.
Do-san. Good luck!
Thanks.
See you.
Gosh, that startled me.
This wasn't the wind.
SAND BOX IS ROOTING FOR YOUR DREAMS
You're here.
Here.
Are the developers running late?
Well… They called this morning,
and they're backing out.
Why?
The lead developer is having a baby soon.
Su-jin is getting married soon, too.
They say they don't want to take the risk.
Well, what can we do?
We have no developers now.
Will it be okay?
Let's go.
We'll see if we can recruit some here.
In-jae?
No way, she's in the US.
That's what the autographed ball said.
That's what the baseball said.
The problem is, there are too many
following their dreams.
I know.
I hope I don't get crushed to death.
And they've already been screened once?
-Stop it.
-No, I won't.
Stop it.
Excuse me. Coming through.
Relax.
I'm extremely nervous.
-Why? You're a man.
-Aren't you nervous?
It's starting.
The 12th Sand Box residency program
applicants, welcome.
I'm Yoon Seon-hak,
the director of Sand Box.
Sand Box was started
by successful entrepreneurs
to help fledgling entrepreneurs
and became Asia's largest
start-up accelerating center.
ACCELERATING CENTER: ORGANIZATION THAT
INVESTS IN AND TRAINS START-UPS
Let me compare start-ups to cars.
For one reason or another, the cars you're
in right now aren't moving forward.
Some of you may have
just jumped in brand-new cars.
Some of you may be sitting
in broken-down cars
that won't start.
And some of you
may have just switched cars.
To make a car move,
you step on the accelerator, right?
-Yes!
Sand Box was created to be
your accelerator.
What is he doing here?
Now, the first step
-is to form teams.
-Is he someone you know?
Some of you have already found
everyone you need,
but not all of you have.
Some people even came alone.
The right to choose teammates
is given to the CEO,
the person whose job is to steer the car.
Out of the 400 people here,
only 40 get to become CEOs.
Only 40?
Each team can have up to five members
and will compete in a three-day hackathon.
The five teams chosen by the investors
in the hackathon
will be accepted into Sand Box.
That's tough.
We're one. We'll stick together
whether we win or fail, okay?
-You bet. Needless to say.
-Hands in, guys.
One, two, three.
-Do-san…
-Chul-san…
Forget it.
Gosh.
CHEONG-MYEONG CORN DOG
HACKATHON LIVE BROADCAST
The whole process is being broadcast live
on the Sand Box app.
I know your backgrounds range
from management to accounting,
development, and design.
But none of your backgrounds
or credentials
matter in the CEO selection process.
They don't matter?
Now you're talking.
Is that good or bad for us?
-It's good…
-It's bad…
-It's good.
Now, we'll send you 50 words
start-ups are paying attention to.
Words? What words?
Are you receiving texts?
Within 30 seconds,
send in five start-up keywords
that are most relevant to each word.
What?
My phone is dead, though.
The people who get
the most relevant keywords right
will be chosen as CEOs.
So they want those who know
how to read trends to be CEOs.
That makes sense.
Okay. Let's start.
FINE DUST
Fine dust…
ULTRAFINE PARTICLES
-What?
-Masks.
What do I do? My phone is dead.
My phone is dead.
OLD DIESEL CARS, YELLOW DUST
Why didn't they tell us beforehand?
I'm sure I'm not the only one.
OLD DIESEL CARS
FINE DUST
KEYWORDS HAVE BEEN SENT
ULTRAFINE PARTICLES,
MASKS, EMERGENCY ALERTS
-Yes!
-Masks…
Focus.
SECURITY
That seems hectic. And you don't have
enough time to search the Internet.
It'd be hard even for those
with an insight into trends.
-Wait.
-What?
No. I must be seeing things.
I'm going to start a company,
like you did.
No way.
SHARING
Please.
-Wi-Fi.
-USB.
-Just be quiet.
AI
DEEP LEARNING, SELF-DRIVING
AGING SOCIETY
Gosh, what was it?
Will I be sent home like this?
WINTER OLYMPICS
Winter Olympics…
I'll write down whatever.
BLOCKCHAIN
-Oh…
-How many?
WORK-LIFE BALANCE
-Okay.
-Father.
I'm sorry.
KOREAN WAVE
K-POP
K-POP, WEBTOON
Park Chan-ho.
-I know.
-What?
-TWICE.
-You want to mess it up, don't you?
-K-pop.
-Look up, please.
GAME, K-POP, WEBTOON, TOURISM, BEAUTY
KOREAN WAVE
We're done with all 50 topics now.
Let me announce those who
got the most relevant keywords.
Well…
Congratulations!
397…
397!
Is that my number?
SEO DAL-MI
It is!
There.
WON IN-JAE
NAM DO-SAN
I'm not there. You?
Me neither.
These are the 40 CEOs
who can choose their teammates.
Please come up on stage!
Then we can't be on the same team?
This is ridiculous.
What an absurd way to choose CEOs!
They should've made us code instead.
Then no one could beat Do-san.
Once you enter Sand Box,
recruit a CEO first.
What your company needs is a proper CEO.
Are you saying
I'll never become a good CEO?
Yes.
What is that girl doing there?
That crook?
Isn't that Won In-jae?
Yes.
What do we do now?
What do we do?
What?
This period will be tough.
Isn't that Won In-jae,
the CEO of Nature Morning?
Why would she want to enter Sand Box?
She'd be like a college student
at a kindergarten.
Excuse me. Can you come back later?
SANDBOX AUDITORIUM LIVE BROADCAST
Oh, my Lord.
Lord.
I'm curious to know
what my hotshot sister is doing here
instead of going back to the US.
I'm curious to know
what your hotshot boyfriend is doing here.
What?
What? Do-san?
I'll give you all one hour.
The CEOs on stage will choose
their teammates for the hackathon.
I hope you will choose them wisely.
This person has a nice background.
-What do we do?
-This person…
We're looking for more people.
Oh, so that's your field.
-Are you interested?
-Do you have a team?
I don't have a team yet.
Right. I think so, too.
How long did you work as a developer?
Do-san.
Why are you here?
You have a fancy office.
And you already found an investor.
You're in a Pre-Series A round.
I'm wondering that, too.
What is Nam Do-san doing here?
Here it says you haven't found
any investors yet.
And your only credential is
winning the CODA competition.
I'm sorry
I deceived you, Dal-mi.
You both look so shocked.
Shocked to be fooled,
and shocked to be caught.
Are you saying
you don't even have a shot
at entering Sand Box
if no CEO chooses you?
It's all over now.
He and Seo Dal-mi are through.
What a peculiar response to my prayer.
A response?
Lord.
I decided to work up my courage
and start my own business.
I do have a destination,
but the path is steep and rough.
So I'm not sure if I can handle it.
Please give me the strength to complete
this long, difficult journey.
And please
lead me to find a companion
for the journey.
You must be disappointed.
No.
I'm thankful.
I'm also thankful
for the chance to be a CEO.
Do-san.
Will you recruit me
as the CEO of Samsan Tech?
-What?
-It's not over?
Is that what you want?
I'd like to make you a similar offer.
My team happens to be missing developers
at the moment.
And I'd like to recruit you guys.
What do you say?
What?
I see your credentials are lacking.
If your CEO also lacks credentials,
won't it be bad for everyone?
Who do you choose, me or Seo Dal-mi?
Do-san.
-Excuse us for a minute.
-Sorry.
Do-san, the future of our company
is on the line.
Yes, and it's an amateur
versus a professional.
Put your feelings aside
and make a rational decision, okay?
My choice is the same either way.
It's the same?
Whether you follow your heart or head?
How is that possible?
You guys don't want to be
someone's underlings.
-Of course not.
-Neither do I.
And?
Dal-mi asked us to recruit her
while Won In-jae said she'd recruit us.
See the difference?
-Oh…
There is a difference.
Either we recruit the CEO
or the CEO recruits us, is that it?
Who do you choose? I'll do as you say.
He even put on such a show. He must have
wanted to show off in front of you.
Aren't you angry?
I'm not.
I've felt the urge to show off
in front of someone many times.
Will you be the CEO of Samsan Tech?
Gladly.
-Yes! I win!
-Gosh.
Five for godori, three for gwang,
and two for pi, so ten in total.
And penalties for Mr. Han and Dal-mi.
Also, pay Do-san and I for the gwang.
Come on! Pay up.
Gosh, you guys are professionals.
-I guess it's our lucky day.
-Totally.
Here's your fortune for today.
-Who is it?
-What's that sound?
It's Yeong-sil, a speaker
that only gives irrelevant answers.
It tells you the same fortune every day.
Is that right, Mr. Nam?
-Yes.
-Every single day.
The same thing every day.
Today, the god of fate
will send a gentle breeze
into your peaceful life.
It's the same thing every day.
-It's incredible.
-That's enough, Yeong-sun!
APPLICANT NUMBER 118
COMPANY NAME: ZEST LINE
REASON FOR APPLICATION
I REMEMBER SWINGING OVER THE SAND
MY DAD SPREAD FOR ME
I wish I could at least fall
on sand instead of concrete.
Sand?
WON IN-JAE
You may run into someone
you met briefly in the past,
at an unexpected place.
Be careful.
The person may seem
like a spring breeze at first
but may turn into a strong winter wind
and change your life completely.
In the limited time,
can you come up with a
practical business idea or not.
Do you really think we should let
a high school graduate become the CEO?
Do you have regrets? Dal-mi could've
gone to college instead of me.
You always make the wrong choices.
I started this because
I wanted to win against In-jae,
but I keep getting greedy.
I keep wanting more.
How much did Dal-mi find out?
Mr. Han, wait.
Why did you go to great lengths to
help us even if it meant you had to lie?
Subtitle translation by: Min-jin Kim